# PRADIP DHAKAL



## Contact

**Address:** 

Maitidevi, Kathmandu

**Phone:** 

+977 9861893027

**Email:** 

Dhakalpradeep238@gmail.com

#### **Hobbies**

- Reading
- Listening Music
- Coding
- Hiking

## Languages

- Nepali
- English
- Hindi

# Summary

I am a student keen to learn anything new. I am Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Wellversed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, Java, Python, C, C++, MySQL.

# **Skill Highlights**

- Java
- PHP/Laravel
- Project Management
- Python
- Data Analysis
- HTML/CSS/JS

# **Experience**

**Computer Instructor** – Nov 2018 to Oct 2019 **Baselink Education Foundation**, Madhyapur, Bhaktapur

**Digital Marketing & SEO** – Oct 2020 to Dec 2020 **Green Computing Nepal**, Mid-Baneswor, Kathmandu

# **Project**

**E-commerce Website** – HTML/CSS/Bootstrap/JavaScript/PHP

**Spam Email Detection** – HTML/CSS /Python/Flask/ML

**Web Log analyzer** – C++ with Multi-Threading/HTML/CSS/JS

Other projects on GITHUB: https://github.com/Pradeep-Dhakal

## **Education**

Bachelor of Computer Science: 2019 – Running Sunway International Business School, IUKL.

+2: 2018-2019 JanaPremi College, Kausaltar, Bhaktapur

## **Certifications**

30 Hours Java Bootcamp – Sunway IT & Youth Club

Business Analytics with Excel – Simplilearn